Thank you for watching
ME
Reinforcing the new center
This is a project to strengthen the new center, where you will learn the skills necessary to be the center while digging deeper into the personality of Inoue, who will play the center for the first time in the new song released on the market.
So far, we've challenged you to a quiz about Inoue. 4 incorrect answers and now the prize money is down to 50,000 yen.
How much prize money will remain?
Speaking of Inoue, we all know that he is good at drawing, and this is the most famous of all.
Which one is Mr. Nimura written by Nagi Inoue?
It's easy, so I'll leave it to you.
Here's the first one, Mr. Himura.
What's this?
Here's Mr. Himura, No. 2
He's so kind!
Here's Mr. Himura, number 3.
That's nice. I'm so happy.
Here's Mr. Himura, number 4.
Look!
I think they look alike.
Many people say it's the closest resemblance.
Here's Mr. Himura, number 5.
I don't like this in real life.
There's a touch like this, too.
Other than the correct answer above, the other members also wrote their own drawings.
But you can tell they're all Mr. Himura.
There's something distinctive about him.
Number 5 has an art school touch.
I wonder what it is.
It's a close-up of something that's a little off-putting.
If you exaggerate it, it could be a portrait of the city.
I don't think this is Nagi's touch
Nagi's touch is more of a cartoon pansy style
I thought the first one was Nagi-like...
Wait a minute.
There's a banana on it.
I wonder why... is that the key?
Does Nagi write bananas?
Does Nagi write banana?Does Nagi write bananas?
When asked to write about Mr. Himura, do you think he would write a banana?
Do you think Kakki will write a banana?
I wonder if Kakki would write a banana.
The second and third are a little bit like the touch.
I mean "the touch".
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no...
They're similar, but...
There's no "FORT" or anything like that.
Then this is Inoue.
Mr. Himura, how long did it take you to draw the picture you were asked to draw?
But it took me less than a minute.
It took me less than a minute.
I see.
I think this is a good hint.
It's a little bit...
Did you just do something with Semya?
Ume?
I'll give you 30,000 yen.
That's not expensive.
Let's fight in the minus column.
Let's do it.
Number one.
Will you write "No. 1, banana"?
I only write bananas.
You said only bananas.
Let's see if Mr. Himura is right about number 1.
Wait, wait.
It's like number 1.
Too bad.
Two guesses...
Three points are missing.
That's 10,000 yen.
The correct answer is... number three.
That's it, isn't it?That's it.
I'll take it gently.
I usually write with that touch.
The number one touch.
That's Telepan.
That's right.
It's number 2, a little like the one Inoue wrote, number 3.
Who?
This is a persimmon.
It looks a lot like this.
I was trying to get Nagi-chan's touch.
I was trying to.
I was trying to pull it off... because you wrote everything so gently.
I thought it would be gentle.
I see. That's great.
Like Mr. Himura after he died.
He was a good guy.
At the time of Parker's death.
He said they were dead people.
Parker?
Put on this triangle.
Parker.
And number four.
Who's this?
Number 4 is... this is Ogawa.
Wow!
He's so good!
I thought you had talent.
You're good.
Inoue-san's greatest feature.
Inoue-san's most distinctive feature, he drew the implants first.
There's a line right there.
That's right.
You forgot the mole.
Yes, it's Inoue-san's charm point.
You've done a good job.You did it... say something about moles.
And number five.
This one. This one.
That's Yoda.
But you know what?
I just cut out a part of a gourmet meal.
It happens every once in a while, doesn't it?
Why does it always end up like this?
You're so good at this!
Wise words!
I thought it was a really nice quote!
It's like a piece of colored paper that Mr. Himura left at the restaurant.
Next is the final question, and the winner is Kawasaki. If he gets it wrong, he gets zero yen.
10,000 yen! I really want you to collect it no matter what!
I'll do my best.
Question: What made Inoue Nagi's mother cry?
Yes, sir.
Four points.
The first time she left her rice.
Yes, I did.
No.2 she made a hole in the wall of her room.
Yes.
Number 3, cut my own hair from the roots in bunches.
Number 4, I had a brother who was 10 years younger than me.
Which one is it?
I don't think I'd ever do something as violent as a bowel movement.
I don't think I'd do anything violent.
But I think number 3 is surprising.
Number 3.
My sister once cut her hair like Kintaro's, right at the base of the bangs.
It reminded me of that.
From a mother's point of view, but there's also number 2, isn't there?
She cut a hole in her room.
I wonder how big a hole she made.
I made a hole in the shape of my own person.I've made a hole in my own humanoid.
I don't know if I'll ever get out of here like that.
I'm going to cry.
I've decided...
The correct answer is number 3.
Himuro-san... are you sure this is the right answer?
What kind of expression is that?
He's falling asleep.
What's wrong?
Correct!
You got it!
Congratulations, you got it right.
There it is.
It means you cut your own hair by the width of it.
What does this mean?
When I was a little girl, I tied my own twin-tails with rubber bands.
Yes, yes.
They get tangled.
Tangled? Rubber bands...
With rubber bands, my hair would get all tangled up and I couldn't get it out.
My mom would get mad if she found out.
I thought if I pulled it out from the roots, she wouldn't know.
Pulling out twin-tails is such a hard job, isn't it?
It's really scary.
But you can't pull it out.
So I went down to the root here and cut it all off.
I've already cut it from the end of the rubber band.
If it's gone from the root, it doesn't exist.
What?
This is where I was when I was in the first grade.
First grade.
Do you remember how long it was, overall?
It was a lot longer than it is now when I was little.
huh?
I went to the store to see what I was going to do to my mom and she cried
What are you doing?
I'm gonna go get some twin-tail ice cream.I'll take twin-tail ice cream for this one.
Thank you.
You should all get some ice cream.
Yay!
It's like we brought you something.
Boom!
And here it is, Bananaman, host of Nogizaka Construction Workers' Chronicles.
Please!
Here we go! Nogizaka!
Yay!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Aww...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yeah!
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Now then, Hiro, please announce today's project. 33rd single hit key
me
Well, we have a hit period before the single, but this time it's also released on August 23rd.
The 33rd single, "To Heaven with Breathless
Booooooooooooooooooooooo no!
I'm sorry, I went there on the wrong day.
I've been there, and I feel like I've done something heavenly on my own... like an all-you-can-eat cake on a day location.
The 33rd single hit period!
Shoes... soccer shoes...
33rd single hit period Inoue NAGI's 30
33 for one
Hahahaha 33rd single hit period Inoue NAGI's 33 people per person thank you campaign!
For this hit period, Inoue, who is playing the center for the first time, went to her hometown by herself as a "Hitori-sama Heaven".
While visiting memorable places, she will thank 33 of her friends and benefactors for their kindness and support.
Inoue will report that he has become the center of the group and campaign for the new song.
Almost this.
That was the other day.
When I was in high school, I was mostly involved in club activities.
We had morning practice, then class, then club activities, then back home.
I did it on weekdays and holidays.
I was in the ball club.This is the ball club!
The members of the same grade are all good friends.
I still hang out with them and go out to eat with them.
I ended up changing high schools.
But I still want to keep in touch with them.
I think they are people I want to stay in touch with now and in the future.
Let's start with the rice bowl club.
That brings back memories.
I'm so glad.
I used to walk home.
It took me an hour or so from home.
If I took the train, I'd have to walk about 10 minutes to get here.
I would go by myself.
I used to walk home alone.
Fuji from the high school.
Fuji, so I decided to come here.
Fuji in the summer sunset.
It was so beautiful and I was secretly looking forward to it.
Oh, the dojo!
This dojo is distorted in many places.
It leaks, the lock won't lock, you can't get in, you can't close the cutter.
I couldn't get in, and the cutter wouldn't close.
It was a tough time.
I can see that everyone is still using it beautifully.
It's still so beautiful.
I miss it
It's beautiful.
Wow, wow, wow.
I didn't know people did this with their pockets.
What?
You know, you get four in a single touch.
And when you hit all four, it's called a pocket.
I've done that a few times.
You mean they're all going in?
I took it pretty seriously.
I liked it.
I want you to do it.I want you to do it.
You used to spring up in Asaren every day.
I used to come in at 5:30 in the morning.
I'd get a little exercise.
I'd walk to school for at least an hour.
I'd do Asaren, and then I'd go to class.
I'd do club activities.
I would go to cram school at home.
I would come home around 11:00 p.m.
That's my daily routine.
It's hard work.
The head of the club?
She was someone I could talk to about all kinds of things.
Like about auditions.
I told her that I wasn't sure if I wanted to go for it or not even before I got it.
I think she was the only one
She thought about it with me.
So every time I passed an audition
I contacted her first.
That's how it all started.
You scared me.
What? Did you get it?
Oh, wait, you scared me.
Could this be...
It's a cucumber.
What a surprise!
My best friend Kanako, the head of KyuDobu...
Without telling Inoue, she gathered all the members of the same class.
I asked everyone to share their memories of Inoue at that time.
It's been a long time since we've met!
There's nothing but strange people today.
I've only seen weird stuff.
You haven't returned my money at all.
What, image-pulling?
What?
I want my money back.
I'll take that as a yes.Accept this.
Nagi has to go home first.
He says he'll go home first, accepts the money and says he doesn't want the change.
Don't take it.
I don't want it.
What should I do?
I have to show my embarrassment in a good way.
It's true.
It's really different from the character and image I've had since I joined Nogizaka.
It's probably too different.
I'm sure you'll come back to it.
I laugh.
I'm laughing.
What are you doing?
When I was in the club, of course I caused you a lot of trouble.
I did the same when I joined Nogizaka.
And of course I'm grateful for that, including before.
But even though I've moved to a different school and have been involved in various activities
But even though I've had to change schools and do all kinds of activities, you've always kept in touch with me.
And you still see me.
I'm surprisingly happy that they still treat me the same way they did back then.
I'm surprisingly happy
He's so cool.
Inaho, who transferred to Nogizaka to join Nogizaka and did not graduate from the school as a member of the school's "Biyudo" club.
Since we were all here, we had to practice together for the first time in about two years wearing our uniforms.
I was so happy!
It could be really bad.
I've been working really hard.
I've been working so hard on my club activities, I wish I could pocket all of this.
That's cool.
That's super cool.
Really? - Yeah. Is this another commercial?
Laughing.
You're right.
It's gonna hit the spot.
What's that?Huh?
I didn't get it.
I'll take a bow.
After that, I continue practicing with my friends.
Most of the members, including the dogs, were holding a bow for the first time in a long time after retirement.
It was indeed quite difficult to hit the target
By the way, when we finally hit the target
Yes!
That's good!
So this time, we prayed for a hit.
The first air to hit the target is a very good performance.
We asked Inoue to shoot 4 arrows just like in the game.
We asked Inoue to pray for a sudden hit to see if he could hit the target with even a single shot.
In practice, he didn't hit the target even once.
How cool!
It's so cool!
It's so hard!
Two hits.
I'm nervous
I like it.
You've got cancer all at once.
Go for it!
Thank you for watching.
Yeah, it's very picturesque.
You guessed it.
Wow!
That's great!
Yeah!
Yes!
I've got it, Center Inon.
I hit the target with the first one!
The other three I couldn't hit, but...
The challenge I gave you out of the blueA task I gave you out of the blue
One person gets one chance to win!
I got it!
It's been a while since I've had someone say "yes" to me, so I was very happy.
So, that's the purpose of this trip
Campaign for progress to the friends who have been so kind to me.
Please give my best regards to Yohitorisama Hitori Tengoku!
I'm sure she's the one.
A campaign of thanks to the six friends in the country
Thank you for everything you've done for me
Thank you for today
I don't think we'll have the chance to do ℃-ute together
I don't think we'll have the chance to do ℃-ute together.
I'm so happy.
It's not that I feel so far away from you, but...
I heard you're prettier than I thought you'd be.
That's nice. I can say that because I'm a supply student.
That's so nice. That's so emo.
It's like we're best friends.
You're far from being a loner.
They're all friends.
That's right.
I'd also like to thank the teachers at my old school who helped us out this time.
I'd like to give you a report and thank you for your help at the center.
When I was a sophomore, I had a problem with English.
I wasn't very good at English.
Even when I was fighting sleep.
It's embarrassing.
After this, the teachers who took care of Inoue when he was in school...
who helped Inoue when he was a student.
The campaign was carefully cleared.
I think this might be the first time I've seen teachers without masks.
They've been wearing masks the whole time.
Inoue-chan is also wearing a mask.
Tanino Sensei is cheering for us.
Ishii Sensei, too.
Really.I'm really...
I'm sorry you're not here.
But I'm glad you're here.
I'm really glad to have this opportunity to say thank you.
I'm really, really happy to have this opportunity to say thank you.
Thank you very much.
Only 20 places left.
The Gratitude Local Campaign Continues
by H.
When we get together, all we do is talk about love
We can't keep up without each other
I couldn't get through to the people I love
who would you be without me?
sorry, you're out this day, I'll call you on the poison mutation
a simple promise, or cancel it
I'm so embarrassed, I'm so urgent, I'm so urgent, I'm so urgent
For the sake of love, forsake all friendship
Then I'll not miss you.
I'd rather not be the last to go back
It's a single life
I'm a carefree, single man in heaven
No need to stop, no need to be at peace
I can be who I really am
It's all right, you can keep it
Oh, love's always a struggle I've lived my life with a sense of normalcy
When you fall in love, it's a big deal, and it never stops
Oh~~~
One man's heaven
I won't be pushed around anymore
It's a single life
There's nothing beyond me
It's a single person's heaven
There's no stopping me
I'm so envious of the days
I can be who I really am
It's okay, it's okay
Save it for meSave it for
one by one
Heaven.
Final message from Hayakawa, who is graduating from the group
Thank you so much for your support and for watching
Thank you so much for your support and for watching "Nogizaka Kenkenchu".
I'm sure you will be able to see the members of Nogizaka from the other side of the screen.
I would like to support Nogizaka even more than you all do.
I hope that you will continue to support Nogizaka as much as I do.
Thank you very much for your support.
Congratulations on your graduation!
I know I brought some air from Mt.
Fuji... but we're still getting used to it.
But they talked a lot with us bananaman at the very beginning.
I really felt like you connected with us, so it was very helpful.
Thank you very much.
Hayakawa's graduation commemorative photo book will be on sale on the 29th, and tickets are now on sale to watch the Tokyo performance of the national tour.
Tears at the sudden surprise next time
This is Seira Hayakawa. My lucky item these days is a frog item.
I hope you all will subscribe to my channel tomorrow!
Bye bye!